redbet.com 2013-04-14

# About us | Redbet

Redbet is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of the Personal Information of all visitors to this website who have submitted their personal details. As part of that commitment, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to reflect the current needs of our visitors to know what information about them we collect, why we collect it, and where it goes. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy.

We have notified the Commissioner of Data Protection about the processing of data in accordance with the requirements of the Data Protection Act (Chapter 440 of the Laws of Malta).

## What are Personal details?

Personal details comprise any information about you that identifies you or by which your identity can be reasonably determined.

## What kind of Personal details about you do we collect and hold?

Redbet only collects personal details that are necessary for one or more of our functions or activities. The personal details that are collected from our clients include: name, address, date of birth, contact information, payment card details, details of betting transactions and account transfers and any other information clients wish to provide or are required to submit in order to satisfy regulatory and statutory requirements.

## How do we collect Personal details from you?

Personal details may be submitted to our website. You will be asked to provide your personal details for the purpose of registering with Redbet and opening and maintaining an account with us.

A "session cookie" is used to enable you to leave and re-enter our website without re-entering your password. Our web server will record the pages you visit within our website.

Where possible, we will give you the opportunity to decline to provide any personal details we request, but in some cases your use of this website may be restricted if you do not provide the requested information.

## How will your Personal details be used?

Redbet will process your personal information in order to: administrate your account; maintain our accounts and records; monitor website usage levels; satisfy regulatory and statutory requirements; maintain the quality of the service we provide to you; and, to inform you, from time to time, about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Redbet will also retain such information and may analyse it if asked to do so in order to investigate any actual or alleged criminal activity or, in respect of any event featured on our website, any threat to the integrity of that event and/or breaches of the rules of that event as laid down by the relevant governing (including sporting) bodies. All rights concerning the storing of your Personal details by Redbet (including copyright and database rights) are and shall remain the property of Redbet.

You are reminded that you, at any time, have the right to request Redbet not to send you any marketing material.

## To whom and how may personal information be disclosed?

It is Redbet’s policy not to disclose our customers’ information to any third party.

However, Redbet may be required to disclose your personal information under certain conditions.

Sometimes, we are required or compelled by law to disclose your personal information. For example: we may disclose your personal information to a court of law in response to a subpoena or to the Inland Revenue Department following a direction issued under taxation laws.

We may also disclose your personal information where you have consented to us doing so. Your consent to the disclosure of your personal information may be given explicitly such as in writing, or verbally, or may be implied from your conduct such as when you discuss details of the relationship you have with us publicly with the media.

Additionally, your personal information may be disclosed to any regulatory or sporting body in connection with policing the integrity or enforcing the rules of a sport or game and/or for the prevention and detection of crime and with parties with whom Redbet has agreements from time to time for the sharing of such data and where Redbet considers that there are reasonable grounds to suspect that you may be involved in a breach of such rules or the law, have knowledge of a breach of such rules or the law or otherwise pose a threat to the integrity of the relevant sport or game. Those bodies may then use your personal information to investigate and act on any such breaches in accordance with their procedures.

## Consent

By providing us with your personal information and registering with us or logging on to our website, you consent to Redbet processing and disclosing your personal information for the purposes, and in the manner, set out on this page, or as otherwise stated in the Terms and Conditions.

## Access to your personal information

You always have the right to access the information we have about you. To review and update your personal contact details, simply log in to our website with your Username and Password and go to My Account - Settings to edit the information. If you prefer, you can contact our Call Centre/Customer Service using the contact details available on the site. In addition, you have the right to have any inaccurate information corrected and, where applicable, deleted.

It is our right to ask you to provide us with a written request for information we hold about you.

You agree that we may use Personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti fraud checks. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. 

## References

Data Protection Act 2001 (Laws of Malta)

Legal Notice 16 of 2003 (Laws of Malta)

**Version 1.0** **January, 2008**
